Chief Warrant Officer Roy Miller is done following orders
Green Zone is a war, action, adventure film directed by Paul Greengrass.
During the U.S.-led occupation of Baghdad in 2003, Chief Warrant Officer Roy Miller and his team of Army inspectors
are dispatched to find weapons of mass destruction believed to be stockpiled in the Iraqi desert.
Rocketing from one booby-trapped and treacherous site to the next, the men search for deadly chemical agents but
stumble instead upon an elaborate cover-up that threatens to invert the purpose of their mission.
Roy Miller, played by Matt Damon.
Clark Poundstone, played by Greg Kinnear.
Martin Brown, played by Brendan Gleeson.
Lawrie Dayne, played by Amy Ryan.
Freddy, played by Khalid Abdalla.
Maj. Briggs, played by Jason Isaacs.
Green Zone is a 2010 British action thriller film directed by Paul Greengrass and written by Brian Helgeland, based
on the 2006 non-fiction book Imperial Life in the Emerald City by journalist Rajiv Chandrasekaran.
The book documented life within the Green Zone in
Baghdad during the 2003 invasion of Iraq.
The key players in the film are General Mohammed Al-Rawi (Yigal Naor), who is hiding in Baghdad during the invasion of Iraq, and US Army Chief Warrant
Officer Roy Miller (Matt Damon), a Mobile Exploitation Team (MET) leader who is searching for Iraqi weapons of mass destruction (WMD).
Miller finds that the majority of the intel given to him is inaccurate.
His  efforts to find the true story about the weapons are blocked by US
Department of Defense official Clark Poundstone (Greg Kinnear).
The cast also features Brendan Gleeson, Amy Ryan,
Khalid Abdalla, and Jason Isaacs.
Principal photography began in January 2008 in Spain, later
moving to Morocco and the United Kingdom.
Green  ne premiered at the Yubari International Fantastic Film Festival in Japan on 26 February
2010, and was released on 12 March in the United Kingdom, by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics and was a box-office failure, grossing $95
million against a budget of $100 million (excluding marketing costs).
The film explores themes of conspiracy, soldier, iraq
war, weapon of mass destruction, baghdad.
The tone is emotional and intense.